Every time the rain no longer falls, and
I see the sky, I think there's a light.
Back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry?
Blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger!
Bridery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead.
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now!
Though time's all on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest of all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back.
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now!
Though time's not on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything Will take
what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
Trust me, I'm a doctor.
Oh, doctor, my ass!
What kind of doctor carries a giant sword
and the whole submarine
thing is fishy too!
What's your deal? Who is it?
Another pirate crew?
It's Trafalgar Law.
Sir, he's a rookie from the north blue.
Then he must be Straw Hat's accomplice.
The two start trouble with the
celestial dragons on Sabahodian.
While back, but we weren't
able to capture either of them.
He's quite dangerous.
They must be planning
to escape by submarine.
Stop screwing around! Head him over!
What's in it for me?
What's in it for you?
Captain
Law?
Navy battleships are approaching for?
the stern.
Damn it. There's no time.
We gotta escape now.
Prepare for combat.
Team A will
pursue the Whitebeard Pirates.
Team B will stop Blackbeard
and his crew at any cost.
Reinforcements Are coming
from underground do
they ever stop finally
now let's rush them down
Oh wait now what not again?
Oh, my God!
You gotta admit, it's pretty fun to watch!
you didn't forget about me did
you clown you forget about us
another fabulous show though
a bit close for comfort
this time yeah power's not
an issue but control is
tricky you're not kidding
if you're gonna sink this
place at least wait until
we're not standing on it!
Stop this! It's madness!
Not enough that you killed
Whitebeard in cold blood.
Now you're abusing his
power and putting his
own crew members at
risk with this nonsense!
What?
Are you trying to nag me to death?
I don't play nice!
Those days are as dead
and gone as Whitebeard!
No one should have that much power.
They can't stop him.
It's a nightmare.
No one's safe.
This is a warning from the Zeff Odi
Archipelago Emergency Broadcast System.
Following an earthquake at Marineford,
a tsunami is expected to
hit our southern shores.
Everyone please remain calm and listen
carefully for the following
safety instructions.
Those in groves 1 through
39 should relocate to
the elevated northern
groves of 40 through 50.
Boobit, what are you doing?
I'm a nobleman, i'll pay good
money if you let me go ahead.
Please proceed in an orderly fashion.
Those weird robots are crawling
over the crack in the plaza.
Come on, move, follow the
pacifistas and open fire!
Hey, you okay?
I got this, guys.
You two go on ahead without me.
What the heck is going on with you?
I don't know.
There's too much sadness.
What does that mean?
There are all these voices in my head, but
I can feel them disappearing one by one.
Huh? Voices?
We'll show you the meaning of justice!
There!
That's for my friend, you damn murderer!
You're gonna pay for your
crimes and blood, scumbag!
We're sending a message, you hear me?
We rule this world!
Order rules this world!
Got one!
Okay, I know we're all stressed out right
now, but you're losing your mind here!
Pull it together!
Please! Somebody help! I can't
make it! I can't make it!
Kobe!
Hey, wait!
Don't run from me!
We're not losing anymore,
okay? Now stay back!
We'll save you!
You'll be fine! Hear me!
Please, I'm scared!
Leave him!
We're not done fighting,
dammit! But, sir...
The pirates are escaping!
Our job is to enforce justice.
We don't have time to
tend to the wounded. Go!
Yes, sir.
Kill every last one of them!
Show the world what
happens when you defy us!
We've got a man down! Medic!
They're all running away.
Just shoot one and move on.
It's not about winning anymore.
They're bloodthirsty.
They want revenge.
It went straight through him! Run!
Chase them down!
That's my fire!
Even if our enemies are
criminals, this isn't justice.
Their wrongs don't make us right.
If you're a marine, then follow my lead
and strike them down with no mercy!
Funny I don't see anyone stopping me or
even trying are you navy boys scared?
Excuse me friend but why don't
you come on down here no not you
Kizaru!
Chop them now, you idiot!
You know what? Fine!
I don't need this right now!
I've done enough!
They're probably gonna die anyway!
John Bart! Here they come!
Ooh, nice catch!
All right, now submerge!
Don't think I forgot about
what happened on Sabaody.
Time to pay.
Whoa!
These wounds are pretty
bad! Hang in there!
Temp, time to die.
You've done enough!
Huh?
A marine?
Kobe!
There's no point in fighting anymore.
There's no point in killing.
It's over. We won.
We can happen. This?
What is he doing?
I can't move.
Please someone help.
These are human lives.
This is wrong.
They have families, children.
They're our friends and
we're watching them die.
We killed Ace.
Whitebeard is dead.
The pirates don't have
the will to fight anymore.
What are we trying to prove?
What's the point?
There are wounded men out there.
We can save them if we stop fighting.
But no, we're just making
more victims, more casualties.
Those marines have nothing to be proud of.
That's Kobe.
Why are they dying?
What are they even fighting for?
Boy, you better run.
You're wasting my time if you would
impede justice, I have no use for you!
Not exactly what I'd hoped for but
at least I said what I had to say.
No?
A splendid speech touched
my heart and though
they were few those
precious moments of courage.
You showed will change
this world though only the
future will tell if it's for
the better or for the worse.
Inside I'll be right behind you.
I don't think so.
Put your hands up now!
Ooh I'll be.
Ben Beckman.
Hey wait a second.
I know that ship.
Let's move.
What's he doing here?
One of the four emperors and his crew.
It's redhead shakes.
On the road.
It's been a long time, old friend.
Let's end this war.
Shanks, huh?
The bastard who turned my
grandson into a damn pirate.
The whole red hair crew showed up!
But how?
His crew had a run-in with one of
the other emperors just yesterday.
I thought he and Kaido would
still be duking it out for sure.
So, what's he doing all the way over here?
What? Shakes? No way!
I got enough going on.
I don't need you here.
Buggy catch your hat give
it back to Luffy for me.
Why don't you do it I've
been holding on to this
treasure map for a while
hoping I'd bump into you!
Treasure map and I guarantee
it'll suit your fancy.
Oh really I'm supposed to
believe we're such good pals
that you'll give me a
treasure map over a dumb hat?
Oh well I can always
give it to someone else.
Don't be so hasty!
I'll do it for old life's sake!
You sure about this? Huh?
You haven't seen Luffy in ten whole years.
You gonna let him leave without saying hi?
Hmm.
It's been that long, huh?
Captain!
Hurry up!
I know this is cool to watch it
all, but we're going underwater!
Yeah, okay.
Actually wait.
No we're gonna die.
Here Straw Hat forgot this.
Now take it and go.
What is he throwing at us?
I see.
Okay okay you got the hat or whatever.
Now come on hurry up. Right.
It's still too soon I'm afraid.
I'll leave this hat to you I want you
to bring this hat back to me someday.
In good condition and
only once you've become
a great pirate that's our promise Luffy.
I'll keep my word.
And that means I can't see you yet.
Right, Luffy?
All right Shall we begin?
It's gonna be a fun operation, yeah?
Damn it! Stop them!
Do whatever it takes!
Ice age!
They're after the submarine!
The whole sea is freezing over!
Looking good his pulse is steady.
What was that I don't know what happened
but the water around us is turning to ice?
We're diving deeper. Full speed.
I think we're good.
Please, no more stress.
Now, Yasakani's sacred show.
What is it now?
Going deeper.
Hold on tight.
We got lucky once, but we're done for sure
this time. We'll be fine. Keep moving.
Geez, can't they just give it up already?
Wait, he didn't hit them, did he?
They can't die down there! No way!
If they're still alive after that,
I'm afraid Lady Luck
just isn't on our side.
But if we can't sink them
today, we'll sink them tomorrow.
Hey, that's one of our ships.
Why is it taking off on its own?
Hurry up, damn it!
Follow that submarine!
Okay, but I mean, it's already underwater.
Also, I'm pretty sure everyone on it is
dead after those attacks from the Admiral.
Sorry!
They're alive.
I'm certain of it.
With my authority as a warlord of the sea,
I shall pursue and
capture Straw Hat Luffy,
no matter the cost!
Yes, help!
That's great, but, like, how?
Just shut up and go!
Whoa!
It's so hot when she yells at us!
You scum-sucking red-haired
sack of excrement!
You're telling me the
treasure map thing was a lie?
Just having some fun, old friend?
It's been a while, huh?
Screw you!
What did you think that I'd forgive
you for what you did out of kindness?
That I'd forget?
Forget about what?
Don't give me that!
If you hadn't snuck up on me back then,
I never would have eaten that
Devil Fruit and more importantly,
I never would have lost that treasure map.
In other words, I'd?
Be filthy rich instead
of running from the Navy.
Oh, is that so?
Playing it cool.
I should have known.
All these years and you're still a
prodigy when it comes to pissing me off.
You've hardly been here five minutes
and you've already lied and cheated me.
You said you were going to stop the war.
Well, you're about to start
a new one with me right now.
Once a chump, always a chump.
You see that?
Sure did.
Even the emperors can't
escape his trash talk!
He's such a pro.
Captain Back, could you be more perfect?
We will follow you to
the end of the world.
I really did miss you though?
Oh, I'm sure you did.
But wait, these guys
are certified badasses.
If I can catch a ride with my old Gourmet,
I can get off this island scot-free.
What now?
Marco, there's nothing to
gain from fighting anymore.
Just walk away nice and easy.
Hawkeye!
Get back here!
I agreed to fight Whitebeard
and his allies, true.
But red hair is another matter entirely.
You should quit as well.
Your thirst for battle is your undoing.
Every blow you land upon your
enemies, you land upon your own men.
However if anyone here
still hungers for battle
Fine then come we shall be
more than happy to face you
Well teach you want to
try sorry Blackbeard
Pretty as a picture
aren't you i got what i
came for here after all
and i'm not looking for
a fight With you guys
well not yet at least
come on fellas let's pack
it up Zia-ha-ha-ha-ha!
I don't know.
Accept your losses.
Honor the fallen.
Withdraw from battle.
With your dignity intact.
Thank you.
I think it's finally over now.
As for Whitebeard and Ace,
I'm sure you won't object to their
friends taking care of the burial.
The battle was already
broadcast to the entire world.
I won't allow you to make a
further spectacle of their
deaths by parading their
corpses around like trophies.
And why shouldn't we?
If they wanted a proper burial so badly,
that perhaps they shouldn't
have defied the navy.
We have every right to
string the bastards up.
And why should we listen
to a pirate anyway?
It's our victory.
We earned it.
That's enough.
But, sir!
I'll allow it, Shanks.
Just this once. But why?
Let me take responsibility.
Thank you.
Now go treat the injured
before it's too late.
This war is over.
That Navy has won.
If you can help the medics, hop to it.
Get those with serious
injuries out of here first.
We've seen enough suffering for today,
and I won't lose any more
men and thus what would later
be known as the war of the
best ended in Marine Ford,
the most fearsome battle since the
beginning of the great pirate era,
brought victories and defeats alike,
leaving the world uncertain of its future?
Thank you.